so obviously as uh Christian as my
parents are they did not take it super
well when I came out of the closet
mostly because I did not come out of the
closet they read my journal when I was
17.
um yes gasp is right
um
it was rough because at that point in my
life my journal was less of like an
introspective thoughts and dreams
journal and more of just a buzzfeed list
of guys dicks I was sucking you know
like uh no content to sift through just
straight to the headlines
it was click bait for my parents uh they
couldn't resist they had to see it it
was tough for them but what's even
funnier so I mentioned I was adopted I
have two adopted siblings they're
biological to my mom and dad and I have
an older brother and a couple of years
ago he also came out of the closet which
is like well you know like I couldn't
have planned a better prank you know
like that
you pumped them good Jesus I can't
oh it's so funny it's so delicious to me
because my parents they really like they
truly rolled the dice there you know
like they made one themselves they got
one off the rack and they both turned
out gay you know like
I don't know what the scientific
argument is there but that feels like
nurture okay that feels like your
fault